function Person(firstName, lastName) {
 this.FirstName = firstName || "unknown",
 this.LastName = lastName || "unknown";
}

Person.prototype.getFullName = function () {
 return this.FirstName + " " + this.Last)
}

function Student(firstName, lastName, school
{
 Person.call(this, firstName, lastName);

 this.SchoolName = schoolName || "unknown this.Grade = grade || 0;
}

//Student.prototype = Person.prototype;



ABOUT ME

Miroslav Furinda

Web developer with creative mindset towards digital challenges and approximately nine years of practical experience. I generally code in PHP / Javascript and their frameworks. I believe my strongest characteristics are reliability, orientaion on detail and preference towards stable solutions instead of quick fixes.

Work Experience

March 2015 - Jan 2019

Oct 2013 - Sep 2014

Feb 2011 - Sep 2013

CCT Marketing International Limited, Ireland

Web Developer

- programming web application for executing and managing intelligent multi-channel digital marketing
- task analysis / implementing
- backend / frontend development
- database model design and implementation
- peer code reviewing and testing
- live deployment

Digitask / Wiktor Leo Burnett, Slovakia

Web Developer

- analysis, design and development of web projects
- simple Linux server administration (Apache configuration, mail server configuration, managing DNS records)
- projects' time estimation
- coding Facebook applications / games

MUW Digital / Muw Saatchi & Saatchi, Slovakia Web Developer

- analysis & development of websites
- internal tools implementation
- developing HTML newsletters
- cross-browser and cross-platform testing
- projects' time estimation

Education

2014 - 2015

National Collage Of Ireland, Dublin/Ireland

Data Analytics

2004 - 2010 FRI, University of Žilina, Žilina/Slovakia Informatics

2000 - 2004 Secondary Industrial School, Levice/Slovakia

Electronics

Skills

Languages • English • Czech

Professional PHP (Yii / Laravel framework, Wordpress)

Javascript / jQuery

• Git, Mercurial

relational DBs (MariaDB, MySQL)

Linux / Unix administration basics

experience with various Web APIs

• working in Agile environment

team player

• creative thinker

strongly goal and detail oriented

Interests

Personal

yoga and movement, books, music, technologies and long nature walks